Guide to the Small Towns Institute Records 1956-2002 (bulk 1969-1997)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Article submissions and drafts, 1966-2002; IV
  - Knox, Jerry – Surviving Post Disaster (Box-folder 106-4)
  - Knox, Jerry – Volume Chain Stores, 1991 (Box-folder 106-5)
  - Koreya, Mele – Nebraska Community Improvement, 1981 (Box-folder 106-6)
  - Kotval, Zenia and Mullin, John R. – When the Mall Comes to Town, 1992 (Box-folder 106-7)
  - Kozel, Ronald M. – Planning for Chemical Spills (Box-folder 106-8)
  - Kunstler, James H. – The Geography of Nowhere, 1993 (Box-folder 106-9)
  - Kurlick, Keith – Viva: Cuba, Missouri, 1987 (Box-folder 106-10)
  - Kurtz, Steven K. – Mills, Wyoming, 1988 (Box-folder 106-11)
  - Labadie, John – Emergency Management, 1984 (Box-folder 106-12)
  - Landon, R. Ned – Kona Arts Center, 1985 (Box-folder 106-13)
  - Landry, Chris – Carbondale, Colorado Community Ski, 1988 (Box-folder 106-14)
  - Lankford, Sam – Government Camp, Oregon, 1988 (Box-folder 106-15)
  - Lannon, Kurt M. – 10 Ways for Government’s to get More Grant, 1992 (Box-folder 106-16)
  - Lapping, Mark – Service Learning in Rural Context, 1992 (Box-folder 106-17)
  - Larson, E. Anne – Touring Arts Teen, 1985 (Box-folder 106-18)
  - Lavender, Marguerite – Lenox, Georgia, Governors Project, 1981 (Box-folder 106-19)
  - Leach, Mary – Sculpture Garden, Owatonna, Minnesota, 1981 (Box-folder 106-20)
  - Lehr, John C. – Canadian Murals, 1983 (Box-folder 106-21)
  - Leightin, Julia – Workers Buy a Factory, 1982 (Box-folder 106-22)
  - Leistritz, F. Larry – Why People Leave Town (Box-folder 106-23)
  - Lemke, June Canty – Keeping Teachers in Small Districts (Box-folder 106-24)
  - Lenda, Helen – Participatory Design and Planning, 1997 (Box-folder 106-25)
  - Leonard, Timothy – Urban Country / Small Towns, 1980 (Box-folder 106-26)
  - Leuci, Mary Simon – Word From Missouri, 1989 (Box-folder 106-27)
  - Lew, Allan – Bringing Tourists to Town, 1985 (Box-folder 106-28)
  - Linder, James R. – An Analysis of Pike Company, 1995 (Box-folder 106-29)
  - Lins, Sue A. – National Park Service and Preservation, 1991 (Box-folder 106-30)
  - Litmar, Todd – Bicycles, Olympia, Washington, 1990 (Box-folder 106-31)
  - Lopata, Roy H. – Taxing Business Costs to Serve, 1984 (Box-folder 107-1)
  - Lowitt, Peter – Preserving the Historic Mill Village, 1994 (Box-folder 107-2)
  - Ludtee, Richard – ARCH, Rural Health Care, 1989 (Box-folder 107-3)
  - Lynch, Rodney C. – Bethel, Maine, 1990 (Box-folder 107-4)
  - Maca, Martin – South Dakota Grain Elevators, 1998 (Box-folder 107-5)
  - Mallahey, James T. – Waterford, New York, 1982 (Box-folder 107-6)
  - Maragiri, Chinna Karthi – How Rural Citizens Perceive the Effectiveness of Crime Prevention Measures in Kentucky, 1987 (Box-folder 107-7)
  - Martin, David K. – Confronting Change in Rural Communities, 1996 (Box-folder 107-8)
  - Mason, Robert – Saving Place, 1995 (Box-folder 107-9)
  - Masterson, Ikuro – Waterfront Design, 1981 (Box-folder 107-10)
  - Mattson, Gary – Community Viability Analysis, 1996 (Box-folder 107-11)
  - Mattson, Gary – Iowa Towns, 1989 (Box-folder 107-12)
  - McCormack, Peter J. – Ethnography, Sense of Place, 1996 (Box-folder 107-13)
  - McEwen, Douglas – Private Campgrounds, 1988 (Box-folder 107-14)
  - McKey, Larry F. – Annexation, A Planners Vision, 1981 (Box-folder 107-15)
  - McNeese, Larry – Palisades, Colorado, Golf Course, 1987 (Box-folder 107-16)
  - McNicol, Barbara – Canmore, Alberta, 1996 (Box-folder 107-17)
  - Meehan, Patrick J. – Cookbook Approach to Development, 1983 (Box-folder 107-18)
  - Meek, Mary – Bonapart, Iowa, 1994 (Box-folder 107-19)
  - Mehroff, Arthur – The Minnesota Design Team, 1995 (Box-folder 107-20)
  - Meier, Marian – Clarion, Iowa, Festival, 1982 (Box-folder 107-21)
  - Mellen, Fred J. – Innovative Ideas at Work, 1995 (Box-folder 107-22)
  - Mieser, Edward J. - Eugene, Oregon, 1981 (Box-folder 107-23)
  - Miles, Jo N. – Toppenish, Washington, 1988 (Box-folder 107-24)
  - Miller, John E., 1994 (Box-folder 107-25)
  - Modisett, Sandra A. – North Dakota Recreation, 1990 (Box-folder 107-26)
  - Moer, Jane and Moer, Kelly – Dakota Leaders, 1992 (Box-folder 107-27)
  - Moon, Henry – Interstate Village, 1989 (Box-folder 107-28)
  - Morril, Dan L. – Keeping History in Historic Preservation, 1983 (Box-folder 107-29)
  - Muench, David – Non-computerized Survey, 1989 (Box-folder 108-1)
  - Mullin, John, 1997 (Box-folder 108-2)
  - Munsell, Ken – Governor’s Project, 1981 (Box-folder 108-3)
  - Munsell, Ken – Movie Palaces and Civic Centers, 1981 (Box-folder 108-4)
  - Murray, Bruce H. – Reasons for Façade Improvements, 1988 (Box-folder 108-5)
  - Murray, Bruce H. – Success in Community Revitalization, 1989 (Box-folder 108-6)
  - Muschell, James E. – Cheboygan, Michigan, Opera House, 1988 (Box-folder 108-7)
  - Muse, Ivan D. – One Room School, 1988 (Box-folder 108-8)
  - Napoli, Donald S. – Preservation, Point Arena, California, 1991 (Box-folder 108-9)
  - Naylor, Amy R. – Democracy confirmed, 1992 (Box-folder 108-10)
  - Neihaus, Charles R. – Jefferson, Indiana, Preservation, 1985 (Box-folder 108-11)
  - Nellis, Lee – Zoning Vicious Cycle, 1984 (Box-folder 108-12)
  - Nelson, Edwin C. – Community School Revitalization, 1996 (Box-folder 108-13)
  - Nelson, Edwin C. – No Town has to Die, 1990 (Box-folder 108-14)
  - Nelson, Roberta – First Class Waterfront Park, 1986 (Box-folder 108-15)
  - New Jersey Villages on Display, 1983 (Box-folder 108-16)
  - Newcomb, Joan M. – Kilpi Hall, Community Center, 1982 (Box-folder 108-17)
  - Nilson, Ralph – Positive Alternatives to a Lack of Funding Rural Education, 1987 (Box-folder 108-18)
  - Norris, Parrell – Motels and Cabin Courts, 2001 (Box-folder 108-19)
  - Nylander, Donna – Creating Children’s Theatre, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 108-20)
  - Oberdorf, Jeff – Felton, California, Town Plan, 1987 (Box-folder 108-21)
  - Ohman, Marian M. – Youth as Historians, 1988 (Box-folder 108-22)
  - Orland, Brian – Computer Visualization, 1987 (Box-folder 108-23)
  - Owen, Melisa – Intergenerational / Entrepreneurship, 1996 (Box-folder 108-24)
  - Paddock, Curt – Campus and Community, 1982 (Box-folder 108-25)
  - Palmer, Arthur E. – Environmental Planning, 1984 (Box-folder 108-26)
  - Pape, John – Adopt a Neighborhood, 1996 (Box-folder 108-27)
  - Paradis, Thomas – Developing a Sense of Place, 1996 (Box-folder 108-28)
  - Patrick, Kevin – Structure of Roadside Cultural Landscape, 1991 (Box-folder 108-29)
  - Patton, Carl V. – Company Towns, 1980 (Box-folder 108-30)
  - Patton, David – Capital Availability in Idaho, 1990 (Box-folder 108-31)
  - Pavy, Manon – Ponchatoula, Louisiana, 1993 (Box-folder 108-32)
  - Peeders, Ken – Fergus Falls, Minnesota, 1982 (Box-folder 109-1)
  - Pivo, Gary – Community Character, 1992 (Box-folder 109-2)
  - Presidential Candidates, 1980 (Box-folder 109-3)
  - Proell, Duane J. – Aquatics Center, 1986 (Box-folder 109-4)
  - Pulver, Glaen C. – Shopping Center, 1983 (Box-folder 109-5)
  - Pybus, Dean – Playscape Construction, 1995 (Box-folder 109-6)
  - Rathge, Richard – Impact of Growth, 1984 (Box-folder 109-7)
  - Richard, Will – Job Creation in Maine, 1980 (Box-folder 109-8)
  - Richardson, Jean – The Epic Project: Rural Vermont, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 109-9)
  - Root, Kenneth – Plant Impacts, Plant Closure, 1998 (Box-folder 109-10)
  - Root, Kenneth – Response to Plant Downsizing, 2001 (Box-folder 109-11)
  - Rossi, Clifford – Investment in Rural Sewers, 1991 (Box-folder 109-12)
  - Roth, Mary Beth – Efland Creeks Community Center, 1986 (Box-folder 109-13)
  - Russell, Lowell K. – Kiowa Nation Rural Transport, 1986 (Box-folder 109-14)
  - Ryder, Barbara – Pullman, Washington, Downtown Design, 1988 (Box-folder 109-15)
  - Schenker, Alex – Zero Employment Governments, 1985 (Box-folder 109-16)
  - Schroeder, Fred E. H. – Fourth Diversion, 1982 (Box-folder 109-17)
  - Schulz, Brian L. – South Central Oklahoma, 1991 (Box-folder 109-18)
  - Seachard, Dan – Puyallup Revitalization Project, 1997 (Box-folder 109-19)
  - Seffield, Emilyn A, - Moberly, Missouri Parks, 1989 (Box-folder 109-20)
  - Shaw, Davis – Property Valve Impacts, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 109-21)
  - Shivani, Harrid – Farmland Preservation in New York, 1985 (Box-folder 109-22)
  - Shumway, J. Matthew – Hot, medium and Cold, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 109-23)
  - Sills, Mark R. – Human Services Planning, 1993 (Box-folder 109-24)
  - Sirois, Kathleen – Dealing with Growth, 1995 (Box-folder 109-25)
  - Skelcher, Bradley – Galesburg, Illinois, 1990 (Box-folder 109-26)
  - Skelcher, Bradley – Hot Springs, South Dakota, 1992 (Box-folder 110-1)
  - Skelcher, Bradley – Lessons of Main Street, 1992 (Box-folder 110-2)
  - Skelcher, Bradley – Main Street Project, 1991 (Box-folder 110-3)
  - Smardon, Richard C. – Clayton, New York, Waterfront, 1983 (Box-folder 110-4)
  - Smardon, Richard and Carter, Emanuel – Fort Drum Special Issue, 1990 (Box-folder 110-5)
  - Smith, Everett G. – Decent Places Off the Beaten Path, 1995 (Box-folder 110-6)
  - Smith, George F. – Tennessee Extension Service, 1986 (Box-folder 110-7)
  - Sofranko, Andrew J. – Employment / Quality of Life, 1980 (Box-folder 110-8)
  - Soll, Michael and Wagner, Fritz – Coping with Change, 1991 (Box-folder 110-9)
  - Sonnenberg, Kyle and Sonnerberg, Gerald – Southern Pines, 1999 (Box-folder 110-10)
  - Steiner, Bill – The Future of Downtowns, 1992 (Box-folder 110-11)
  - Stevens, Lauren R. – The Wiliamson Advocate, 1983 (Box-folder 110-12)
  - Stockhouse, Jan – Selling to Employees, 1988 (Box-folder 110-13)
  - Stowkowski, Patricia A. – Colorado Gambling Boom, 1992 (Box-folder 110-14)
  - Stroud, Hubert B. – Transfer of Development Rights, 1992 (Box-folder 110-15)
  - Stubbles, Russell – Deadwood, 1990 (Box-folder 110-16)
  - Summers, Gene F. – Cash Transfer Payments, 1983 (Box-folder 110-17)
  - Sundermyer, Lonnie – Danbury, Connecticut, Friendly Visitors, 1989 (Box-folder 110-18)
  - Sutton, Christopher and Engelstad, Jeff – Growth on the High Planes, 1999 (Box-folder 110-19)
  - Swanson, David A. – 1980 Census for Small Towns, 1987 (Box-folder 110-20)
  - Swanson, David A. – Population of Rural Communities, 1995 (Box-folder 110-21)
  - Sweet, Doug – Astoria, Oregon, Community Radio, 1985 (Box-folder 110-22)
  - Taylor, James H. – Othello, Washington, Health Care, 1984 (Box-folder 111-1)
  - Thomas, Margaret A. – Preservation, Sale Controls, 1980 (Box-folder 111-2)
  - Thorensen, Susan Werner – Portsmouth, New Hampshire, 1988 (Box-folder 111-3)
  - Timmins, Richard H. – Starting a Community Foundation, 1987 (Box-folder 111-4)
  - Tompkins, Judith L. – Bellevue, Michigan, 1984 (Box-folder 111-5)
  - Tripp, Garnet – Hillman, Michigan, 1990 (Box-folder 111-6)
  - Tyler, Norman – Evaluating the Health of Development, 1989 (Box-folder 111-7)
  - Van Otten, George – The Verde Valley, 1992 (Box-folder 111-8)
  - Vance, Bill – Washington Recreation, 1990 (Box-folder 111-9)
  - Waelti, John J. – Cheesemaker’s Lament, 1990 (Box-folder 111-10)
  - Wagner, Fritz – Louisiana Programs, 1990 (Box-folder 111-11)
  - Wagner, Fritz –Single Industry Towns, 1984 (Box-folder 111-12)
  - Wagner, Richard – Preservation Design Week, 1982 (Box-folder 111-13)
  - Walzer, Norman – Illinois Economic Development, 1994 (Box-folder 111-14)
  - Warrack, Allan A. – Mega-projects in Small Towns, 1982 (Box-folder 111-15)
  - Weaver, Glen D. – Creating Special Events, 1988 (Box-folder 111-16)
  - Weber, Eugene J. – Role of Voluntary Organizations, 1996 (Box-folder 111-17)
  - Weegar, W. Allan – Hurst, Texas, Volunteerism, 1983 (Box-folder 111-18)
  - Wells, Betty – Intercommunity Cooperation, 1991 (Box-folder 111-19)
  - Wexler, Clifford – Photo-documentation, 1984 (Box-folder 111-20)
  - Williams, S. Wells – Green River, Wyoming, 1983 (Box-folder 111-21)
  - Williams, Harold S. – Barn Raisings, 1986 (Box-folder 111-22)
  - Williams, Harold S. – Self-help in New York, 1987 (Box-folder 111-23)
  - Williamson, Jack – Design Michigan, 1987 (Box-folder 111-24)
  - Willits, Fern K. – Youth Recreation Preferences, 1988 (Box-folder 112-1)
  - Willoughby, Chuck – Perkins, Oklahoma, 1998 (Box-folder 112-2)
  - Winchell, Dick G. – Wilbur, Washington, 1991 (Box-folder 112-3)
  - Wolber, Ronald V. – Fraser, Michigan Firefighters, 1991 (Box-folder 112-4)
  - Wolensky, Robert – Fiscal Stress in Wisconsin Small Governments, 1991 (Box-folder 112-5)
  - Woods, Michael – Pageantry and Politics in an English Village, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 112-6)
  - Young, Jenny E. – Designing a Health Clinic for Prairie City, Oregon, 1995 (Box-folder 112-7)
  - Young, Jenny E. – Making Vivid Towns, 1991 (Box-folder 112-8)
  - Yuill, Robert S. – Opinion Survey, 11981 (Box-folder 112-9)
  - Everitt, John C. – Changing Rurality in Canadian Provinces, 1997 (Box-folder 112-10)
  - Hartmans, Donna, 2001 (Box-folder 112-11)
  - Holland, Ann H. R. – Keeseville, New York, 1999 (Box-folder 112-12)
  - Jamroz, Steven J. – The Importance of On-Street Parking, 1997 (Box-folder 112-13)
  - Johnson, Peter – Historic Preservation and Urban Waterfront Development, 2000 (Box-folder 112-14)
  - Masilela, Calvin, 1999 (Box-folder 112-15)
  - Mitchell, Martin – Small Town Kansas Revisited, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 112-16)
  - Niemcyzk, Kenneth – Lebanon, New Hampshire Planning, 1999 (Box-folder 112-17)
  - Raento, Pavlina – Tourism and Community Development in Jackpot, Nevada, 1999 (Box-folder 112-18)
  - Rigdon, Michael A. – Policing and Public Housing, 1997 (Box-folder 112-19)
  - St. Jacobs, Ontario (Box-folder 112-20)
  - Walker, Gerald – Neo-Traditional Planning, 1998 (Box-folder 112-21)
  - Wood, Colin – British Columbia, Canada Photographs (Box-folder 112-22)
  - Vasiliev, Ren – U. S. Route 6, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 112-23)
- Photographs for articles, 1972-1991; V
  This series consists of photographs submitted for publication or published in the Small Towns Institute’s journal from 1972 to 1991, the bulk of the images date from 1972 to 1979. The series is arranged chronologically and alphabetically by name of location.
  - Issue Photographs, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 113-1)
  - Issue Photographs – Ellensburg Art Gallery Renovation, May, 1975 (Box-folder 113-2)
  - Issue Photographs, July, 1975-October, 1975 (Box-folder 113-3)
  - Issue Photographs, January, 1976-March, 1976 (Box-folder 113-4)
  - Issue Photographs, April, 1976-August, 1976 (Box-folder 113-5)
  - Issue Photographs, September, 1976-December, 1976 (Box-folder 113-6)
  - Issue Photographs, January, 1977-March, 1977 (Box-folder 113-7)
  - Issue Photographs, April, 1977-June, 1977 (Box-folder 113-8)
  - Issue Photographs, July, 1977-September, 1977 (Box-folder 113-9)
  - Issue Photographs, October, 1977-December, 1977 (Box-folder 113-10)
  - Issue Photographs, January, 1978-June, 1978 (Box-folder 113-11)
  - Issue Photographs, July, 1978-September, 1978 (Box-folder 113-12)
  - Issue Photographs, October, 1978-December, 1978 (Box-folder 113-13)
  - Issue Photographs, 1979 (Box-folder 113-14)
  - Issue Photographs - Alabama (Box-folder 113-15)
  - Issue Photographs - Arizona (Box-folder 113-16)
  - Issue Photographs - California (Box-folder 113-17)
  - Issue Photographs - Colorado (Box-folder 113-18)
  - Issue Photographs - Connecticut (Box-folder 113-19)
  - Issue Photographs - Delaware (Box-folder 113-20)
  - Issue Photographs – Georgia (Box-folder 114-1)
  - Issue Photographs – Idaho (Box-folder 114-2)
  - Issue Photographs – Illinois (Box-folder 114-3)
  - Issue Photographs – Indiana (Box-folder 114-4)
  - Issue Photographs – Iowa (Box-folder 114-5)
  - Issue Photographs – Kansas (Box-folder 114-6)
  - Issue Photographs – Kentucky (Box-folder 114-7)
  - Issue Photographs – Louisiana (Box-folder 114-8)
  - Issue Photographs – Massachusetts (Box-folder 114-9)
  - Issue Photographs – Michigan (Box-folder 114-10)
  - Issue Photographs – Minnesota (Box-folder 114-11)
  - Issue Photographs – Montana (Box-folder 114-12)
  - Issue Photographs – Nebraska (Box-folder 114-13)
  - Issue Photographs – New Hampshire (Box-folder 114-14)
  - Issue Photographs – New Mexico (Box-folder 114-15)
  - Issue Photographs – New York (Box-folder 114-16)
  - Issue Photographs – Ohio (Box-folder 114-17)
  - Issue Photographs – Oklahoma (Box-folder 114-18)
  - Issue Photographs – Oregon (Box-folder 114-19)
  - Issue Photographs – South Dakota (Box-folder 114-20)
  - Issue Photographs – Texas (Box-folder 114-21)
  - Issue Photographs – Utah (Box-folder 114-22)
  - Issue Photographs – Vermont (Box-folder 114-23)
  - Issue Photographs – Virginia (Box-folder 114-24)
  - Issue Photographs – Washington (Box-folder 114-25)
  - Issue Photographs – West Virginia (Box-folder 114-26)
  - Issue Photographs – Wyoming (Box-folder 114-27)
  - Issue Photographs – Canada (Box-folder 114-28)
  - Issue Photographs – Ellensburg, Washington (Box-folder 115-1)
  - Issue Photographs – Leavenworth, Washington (Box-folder 115-2)
  - Issue Photographs – Lester, Washington (Box-folder 115-3)
  - Issue Photographs – Front Covers (Box-folder 115-4)
  - Issue Photographs – Oil Drilling Equipment (Box-folder 115-5)
  - Issue Photographs – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 115-6)
  - Contact Sheets – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 115-7)
  - Anthology of Articles – Volume 1, Chapters 1-4 (Box-folder 116-1)
  - Anthology of Articles – Volume 1, Chapters 5-7 (Box-folder 116-2)
  - Anthology of Articles – Volume 2, Chapters 1-4 (Box-folder 116-3)
  - Anthology of Articles – Volume 2, Chapters 5-10 (Box-folder 116-4)
  - Anthology of Articles – Volume 3, Chapters 1-4 (Box-folder 116-5)
  - Anthology of Articles – Volume 3, Chapters 5-10 (Box-folder 116-6)
- Publications, 1969-2001; VI
  This series consists of publications produced by the Small Towns Institute from 1969 to 2001. The series includes the monthly and bi-monthly news journal Small Town, and indices to the journal and the three volume set of selected articles titled An Anthology of Articles from Small Town.
  - News Journal, 1969 (Box-folder 117-1)
  - News Journal, 1970 (Box-folder 117-2)
  - News Journal, 1971 (Box-folder 117-3)
  - News Journal, 1972 (Box-folder 117-4)
  - News Journal, 1973 (Box-folder 117-5)
  - News Journal, 1974 (Box-folder 117-6)
  - News Journal, 1975 (Box-folder 117-7)
  - News Journal, 1976 (Box-folder 117-8)
  - News Journal, 1977 (Box-folder 117-9)
  - News Journal, 1978 (Box-folder 117-10)
  - News Journal, 1979 (Box-folder 117-11)
  - News Journal, 1980 (Box-folder 118-1)
  - News Journal, 1981 (Box-folder 118-2)
  - News Journal, 1982 (Box-folder 118-3)
  - News Journal, 1983 (Box-folder 118-4)
  - News Journal, 1984 (Box-folder 118-5)
  - News Journal, 1985 (Box-folder 118-6)
  - News Journal, 1986 (Box-folder 118-7)
  - News Journal, 1987 (Box-folder 118-8)
  - News Journal, 1988 (Box-folder 118-9)
  - News Journal, 1989 (Box-folder 119-1)
  - News Journal, 1990 (Box-folder 119-2)
  - News Journal, 1991 (Box-folder 119-3)
  - News Journal, 1992 (Box-folder 119-4)
  - News Journal, 1993 (Box-folder 119-5)
  - News Journal, 1994 (Box-folder 119-6)
  - News Journal, 1995 (Box-folder 119-7)
  - News Journal, 1996 (Box-folder 119-8)
  - News Journal, 1997 (Box-folder 119-9)
  - News Journal, 1998 (Box-folder 120-1)
  - News Journal, 1999 (Box-folder 120-2)
  - News Journal, 2001 (Box-folder 120-3)
  - Articles of Anthology, Volume 1, 1991 (Box-folder 120-4)
  - Articles of Anthology, Volume 2, 1991 (Box-folder 120-5)
  - Articles of Anthology, Volume 3, 1991 (Box-folder 120-6)
  - Comprehensive Index, Volumes 1-10, 1981 (Box-folder 120-7)
  - Comprehensive Index, Volumes 11-12, 1982 (Box-folder 120-8)
- Financial and miscellaneous records, 1969-1997; VII
  This series contains the financial records of the Small Towns Institute from 1969 to 1995. The series includes proposals for the creation of a program to study rural communities directed to Central Washington State College (1966), Articles of Incorporation (1969-1970), correspondence related to the transition of the director, student papers and miscellaneous newspapers clippings, ephemera and loose files associated with the organization from 1969 to 1997.
  - Financial Records, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 121-1)
  - Financial Records, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 121-2)
  - Financial Records, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 121-3)
  - Financial Records, 1984 (Box-folder 121-4)
  - Financial Records, 1985 (Box-folder 121-5)
  - Financial Records, 1986 (Box-folder 121-6)
  - Financial Records, 1986 (Box-folder 121-7)
  - Financial Records, 1987 (Box-folder 121-8)
  - Financial Records, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 121-9)
  - Financial Records, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 121-10)
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1969 (Box-folder 122-1)
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1970 (Box-folder 122-2)
  - By-Laws, 1969 (Box-folder 122-3)
  - Corporate Resolution of Authority, 1979 (Box-folder 122-4)
  - Proposal for Establishment of Institute, 1966 (Box-folder 122-5)
  - Financial Records, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 122-6)
  - Financial Records, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 122-7)
  - Director Transition – Board of Trustees, 1983 (Box-folder 123-1)
  - Director Transition – Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 123-2)
  - Director Transition – Denman loans, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 123-3)
  - Director Transition – Denman resignation, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 123-4)
  - Director Transition – Resolution to the Administration of Central Washington University, 1983 (Box-folder 123-5)
  - Ephemera – Stationery, brochures, etc., Pre-1983 (Box-folder 123-6)
  - Ephemera – Stationery, brochures, etc., Post-1983 (Box-folder 123-7)
  - Ephemera – Stationery, brochures, etc. (Box-folder 123-8)
  - Journal Index Preparation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 123-9)
  - Lease for Space from Central Washington University, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 123-10)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Letters to Editors, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 123-11)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Letters to Editors, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 123-12)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Letters to Editors, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 123-13)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Letters to Editors, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 123-14)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Letters to Editors, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 123-15)
  - Student papers – An Analysis of the Kittitas County Youth Center, 1971 (Box-folder 123-16)
  - Student papers – Cle Elum, A Case Study: Youth Migrations versus Inducements, 1970 (Box-folder 123-17)
  - Student papers – Communal Organizations and the Outside, 1972 (Box-folder 123-18)
  - Student papers – Ellensburg during World War II (Box-folder 123-19)
  - Student papers – The Evolution of Western Forts Suppositions and Revisions, 1972 (Box-folder 123-20)
  - Student papers – Roslyn: The Effect of the Loss of the Mining Industry (Box-folder 123-21)
  - Student papers – The Vocational and Locational Preference Attitudes of 29 Grade Students in Union Gap, 1970 (Box-folder 123-22)